(Sheldon:)Irrelevant. The disruption in your
relationship is making my life intolerable.
(Penny:)Well, I'm sorry, Sheldon,
but this really isn't about you.
(Sheldon:)I don't follow.
(Penny:)Yeah. Yeah, I'll be right there.
Look, Sheldon, I have to go.
All right. Let's assume ad arguendum,
that in this case Leonard is wrong.
(Sheldon:)-Leonard is wrong.
-Considering the transgressions...
...you committed
that he's overlooked...
(Sheldon:)...don't you think that
you could return the favor?
(Penny:)I'm coming. Goodbye, Sheldon.
(Penny:)What do you mean
transgressions I've committed?
(Sheldon:)Were you under the impression that
Leonard has no complaints about you?
(Penny:)Like what? Yeah, yeah, I see you.
You're making a check sign in the air.
Got it. Just hold your horses.
(Penny:)-What does Leonard complain about?
-Your driving.
The stuffed animals on your bed...
(Sheldon:)...that stare at him
during your amorous activities.
(Sheldon:)Your constant tardiness, your singing.
(Penny:)-My singing?
-That's from my list.
Leonard'd be a fool
if he didn't agree with it.